The following programme contains
strong language and violent scenes.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
- Good morning.
- UDC is going to be in Tallinn on the 22nd
We're assuming you've finished
whatever business you had in Munich?
That seems like a
decent assumption.
Elias.
Do you know what happened to
Norman after I called him?
They came for him.
Something went wrong in Belarus.
Norman knew we were
coming. If there's a leak.
it has to be investigated
and resolved.
From here on. keep
the circle tight.
This life. it's not normal.
When are you coming back?
Honestly. I don't know. It's
not good enough. Charles.
Foreign Secretary. Can you
comment on the events in Germany?
Manfred and Elias Fest were not
only close personal friends of mine.
they were fearless defenders of
Western values and our way of life.
"Are you next.
Foreign Secretary?
"Are you worried
for your own safety?
"What does this mean
for your party?"
We have Leckner on video
with an update from the BND.
"The loss of these heroic men
is a terrible tragedy for Germany.
"the German people. and for
Western democracy itself.
"Thank you again."
"The British Foreign
Secretary. Jeremy Whitelock.
"calling the murders of
Manfred and Elias Fest
"a tragedy for Western
democracy itself.
"Around the world.
tributes have..."
"Elias Fest
was murdered a few hours ago
"and it will take time..."
We need to talk.
"However. one thing seems clear.
"Elias Fest hired a professional
assassin to kill his own father.
"Yeah. and apparently. he...
he failed to pay what he owed."
He probably wasn't expecting
to be used as bait.
"The assassin disguised
himself as a limo driver
"and killed Elias en route
to his father's funeral."
And we know this. how?
"Elias called his head of security
er. Muller. from the limo."
Was the call
recorded? "Er. no."
Was it in German?
"Er. no. English."
Age?
"All I have at this time
is not young. not old."
Did anyone get a good look
at him? "It appears not. no."
"How are you getting on
with your investigation?
"Your British gunmaker?"
We have a lead on his brother
we're actively pursuing.
although right now I'm
afraid we don't have anything
significant enough
to share. "I see.
"Meanwhile our assassin
has disappeared.
"Police all over Europe
are looking for him."
Putain! Hey!
Putain!
Anthony Mallison?
♪ Some flowers never get
to bloom and see the day
♪ Some flowers are content
to wish their lives away
♪ Some may rise
♪ And some may fall
♪ But only
♪ You may
♪ Ever
♪ See me true
♪ So only
♪ You can
♪ Tell that
♪ This is who I am
♪ No life
♪ Lonely
♪ This is who I am. ♪
My American friend is
taking a chance on me.
It's not official for 303.
They picked up some chatter.
Hm.
"Rodin price point
agreed. Commencement paid.
"Jackal en route."
Somebody's hiring the
Jackal for another kill.
Rodin? Mean anything to you?
Uh-uh. Could be the buyer?
More likely the target.
Where did they pick
up the chatter?
Wouldn't say.
We need a breakthrough
Bianca. and soon.
Hey?
"Hey." Hi.
"Are you OK?"
Mm-hm.
So. er...
I've been thinking
about what you said.
"And I think you were
absolutely right.
"I think this has
all been too much."
Look. they've got me away
for a few more nights.
but I was wondering
if there was any chance that I
could persuade you to come to Paris.
Paris? "Yeah."
"I thought I could
try and get our room
"at that little place in the Marais.
the one by the Place des Vosges?
"Remember? I thought we could try
and get a table at the San Martin.
"We could talk."
I don't know.
There's a lot that I...
well. that I need to
talk to you about...
that I've been afraid to.
"Please come.
"I checked the flights and there's
a two o'clock from Seville."
Please.
Alright.
Was that a yes? Yeah. OK?
OK.
"I'll sort all the tickets
and stuff. and I'll email you.
OK.
I love you.
Please tell me you've got
something from Sniper School?
None of the names from that list
have been out of the country
in the past few weeks.
But there might be one
who's worth talking to.
George Hands. He runs a sniper
WhatsApp group. He's obsessed.
I'm gonna go talk
to him now. Ah. no.
Text me the address.
I'll go myself.
Hey. I'm not the mole. you know.
It's hardly a bloody
secret. is it?
Everyone's on edge.
Carver's asking for access to
phones and emails of anyone
that knew about Belarus. Watch
Sparrow's phone. If it moves.
let me know.
You're not what I
was expecting. Yeah.
Get that all the time. Can I...?
3.815 metres?
Do you know how far that is?
No.
That's over two - of your English miles.
- Two miles?
Is that right?
Do you know how long a bullet - takes to travel two miles?
- Tell me.
Six. seven seconds.
Like. your target can be
standing by the window
when you take that shot.
and be sitting on the toilet
by the time the bullet shows up.
- Hm.
- You see. when you shoot at that distance.
you are shooting
into the future.
Wow.
Yeah.
Now. your fella...
well. he's probably very good.
but he is one lucky
bastard. I tell you that.
Well. if he's good...
he must be British Army. right?
100 percent.
Could you have made that shot. - back in the day?
- Oh yeah. course.
Standing on me head.
Look. I was one of the best.
but two miles?
I never took a
shot at that range.
Could anyone here have taken it?
That Wilson was a total wanker.
He couldn't hit a barn
door at ten yards.
And Parker's in jail.
Mitchell.
On a good day...
nah.
Nah. He was good.
But. nah. it's just too far.
Must have been a lot of chat
about this on your WhatsApp group.
Oh. course. Its nonstop.
Anyone in the group who
could have made that shot?
Hold on.
You?
What. are you saying
they're suspects?
Oh. I'm just gathering
some background.
Cos none of the lads
could've done it.
And even if they
could. they wouldn't.
Yeah?
Thanks.
Cheers.
The good old days.
Now. we were the
best. Well. not really
cos none of you
could've made that shot.
There is one guy.
Go on.
He was at Stirling Lines.
It was after my time.
But. well. he was
a legend. Who?
Alexander Duggan.
And where can I find him?
Well. first off. you need
to take a plane to Kabul.
- Kabul?
- And then you get yourself down to Helmand.
And you'll find Duggan
just outside Lashkar Gah.
Bits of him. anyway.
I heard Duggan was taken out by
an IED with his entire squad.
Messy.
So. Duggan's dead?
Ten years ago.
Thank you.
You've been so helpful.
You're welcome.
The Sparrow hasn't
moved from the hotel.
"What did Hands have to say?"
Get me everything you can
on Alexander Duggan. Sniper.
Killed in Helmand in 2013.
Well. what's the point.
if Duggan's dead?
Oh. my...
Damian. please just
do it! Fucking do it!
Great. Searching
for dead people.
Street Spirit
♪ Rows of houses
♪ All bearing down on me
♪ I can feel their
♪ Blue hands touching me
♪ All these things into position
♪ All these things we'll
one day swallow whole
♪ Fade out
♪ Again
♪ Oh ♪ La la la
♪ Oh ♪ La. la. la
♪ La la la
♪ Cracked... ♪
Hi.
OK.
Couldn't get our
room in the Marais.
but I did managed to get
us a table at San Martin.
You said you wanna
talk. so talk. or I go.
And I want the truth.
- I go.
- I've been lying to you since the day that I met you.
I love you. Nuria. and
Carlito. That's not a lie.
And it never has been.
But I knew that if I told
you the truth about myself...
then I'd lose you both.
What is the truth?
What do you do. Charles?
I'm a trouble shooter.
What does that mean?
So. big companies. multi-nationals.
when they have a problem.
they send me in to solve it.
A problem? Yeah.
Do you kill people?
No.
No. I don't kill people.
No. It's industrial espionage.
And. usually. it's relatively
straightforward and above board.
Occasionally. it's a
little more complicated.
And. erm sometimes.
very rarely. it's illegal.
Illegal? Sometimes I
use false identities.
Sometimes I buy people off.
- Sounds fucking dangerous.
- The people I work for are billionaires.
The people I investigate are billionaires.
They're all fucking dangerous.
What about your son?
What'd you mean? I can't...
I can't believe you
put our lives at risk.
Oh. no. I've never put
your lives at risk.
Nuria. I've never put
your lives at risk and-
Just to be your
wife. to be your son.
This is a risk for
us. Listen to me.
I'm very careful. and I'm
very good at what I do.
Listen. these people that hire me
they don't know anything about me.
they don't know my name. and-Maybe
you don't know the risk. Charles.
You say they are dangerous.
Dangerous for us.
In a couple of weeks.
this is all gonna be over.
It's gonna be done. I'm through.
I meant that. I'm done with it.
And once this job is done.
we will have enough money
to live the life
that we wanna live.
And it'll be a great
life. Nuria. Oh. come on.
Come on. It'll be a...
It'll be a great life.
The three of us.
Together.
Please believe me.
How can I believe you?
You lied to me.
From the start. you lie.
And now you say.
"Believe me. I don't
want this anymore."
How can I believe you?
Tell me.
How? Because I'm here.
And the only reason that I'm
here in Paris. in this hotel.
in this fucking room. is
because my life is with you.
And if I don't...
If I don't have that. then
I don't have anything.
I like you like this.
Oh. for fuck's sake.
When do you finish this job?
Two weeks.
And then. I promise you.
everything will be the way
that you want it to be.
No more lies. please.
Please.
No more lies.
This Jackal is free to
ply his trade. Fine.
That's liberal economics.
but killing Elias Fest?
Did you. or did you not.
tell the Jackal not to do anything
that would endanger our project?
I did. Explicitly.
I think we need to
find somebody else.
With respect. did he
go off piste in Munich?
Yes. I understand that.
but time is short.
You're not gonna find anybody
as good as the Jackal.
I can get someone from
Special Forces like that.
You went down that route and
it didn't work out so well.
which is why Leonora came to me - first.
- I have an update.
Turns out Elias hired the
Jackal to kill Manfred.
He didn't pay up. so
the Jackal killed him.
OK. that's just sick.
We need to get shot
of this guy. Hang on.
This guy goes back to Munich. a
town that is swarming with police.
to call in an unpaid debt.
To me that speaks of character.
Where is he now? He
should be in Tallinn.
You need to find him
and stay with him.
Well. that would be challenging.
He's not gonna like that.
We're sticking with the Jackal
because you recommended it.
Is that your recommendation?
It is.
Well. on your head be it.
There's still no movement
on Sparrow's phone.
OK.
See you tomorrow.
I've loved you since
the first I saw you.
You were the only girl for me.
And when I was in jail
all those years...
you stood by me.
You came to visit me every week.
You were always there for me.
We had a great life.
Argh!
Oi!
Personal Protection Unit.
Can I have your department
number and personal ID?
"3-0-3-5-2-1-4-5-5-B."
Am I speaking to Bianca?
"Yep. yep. you are." Are
you in danger. Bianca?
I'm being pursued by
a man with a knife.
I'm leading him to Camden Lock.
north bank. south of High Street.
I'm sending you the pin now.
I'm connecting
you now. Stand by.
This is Vincent Pyne."I have an
officer in danger - Bianca Pullman.
"Sending you her
location." Received.
"Stand by."
"Bianca!? It's me. Vince.
"Where exactly are
you?" Lockride bridge.
Are you in immediate danger?
"Well. he's has a knife.
"and he definitely wants to kill
me. but I need this guy alive."
Understood. Keep your
distance till we get there.
"Is he still on you?"
Hang on. he's stopped.
Why has he stopped?
Shit.
Fuck.
He's gone. He's fucking gone.
"I can't lose him. Vince.
This guy's my only lead!"
"OK. be careful.
Stay on the line."
I've got him. North
bank. heading south.
- I'm going after him.
- Almost with you. Don't do anything stupid. yeah?
Larry! Larry stop!
Drop the knife.
Armed Police! Armed Police!
Stay where you are!
Stick your hands up!
Hello. stranger.
Larry. I need you to get on
the floor and drop the weapon.
Larry. drop the-Don't shoot!
Fuck.
Armed Police! Armed Police!
Armed Police!
Who the fuck is that?
She was my asset.
Sparrow.
Alison.
Give it to me straight.
doctor. Is she gonna make it?
She'll pull through.
Oh. my brave soldier.
Oh. fuck you.
Still charming as ever.
What's it like working in PPU?
I've been on secondment for a year.
Waiting for my next assignment.
But. you know. it's good.
I like keeping people safe.
Yeah. I might need
some lessons in that.
You know how it is in this
game. there's always casualties.
The trick is to keep
them to a minimum.
And. look. Larry's
alone in London.
The police are pretty certain
they'll catch him sooner or later.
All done. But...
better safe than sorry.
Thanks. 'Mum! What
happened to your arm?'
Mum?
What happened?
You alright? Yeah.
yeah. I'm fine.
Er. it's been a
night. but I'm good.
Jaz. why don't you go and
finish getting ready for school?
I made a smoothie if you
want some. Thank you.
Oh. God. yeah it's.
erm. Edinburgh today.
Glasgow. Glasgow. sorry.
So. can you tell
me what happened?
No.
OK.
But when you
disappear. for work.
it's really hard to not
imagine worst-case scenarios.
It's really not as bad as
it looks. Can we just-?
And when you say things like
that. it just shuts me out.
Can we just-OK. fine. well. then.
I'll just not go to the conference.
What. no. that's not
what I'm-Well. why not?
I know how hard you've
worked on this paper.
You are going. Dad.
you're gonna slay.
OK. well. apparently.
I'm gonna "slay." so...
Here.
You're good. OK?
OK. OK.
Here.
Look after your
mum. love. Yeah.
Bye.
Do you need to take
some personal time?
No. No. I'm fine. Thank you.
Good.
Any new developments?
No. Not yet.
Bianca. I want to support you.
But Larry escaping is
only just the latest.
We have two field officers dead
in Belarus. an asset murdered.
not to mention her daughter
who died in custody.
And now we have Carver going through
everyone's phones and emails.
It's horribly messy.
and. unfortunately. it
all comes back to you.
Oversight are already
all over this.
There's only so much I
can do to protect you.
We need to make some progress.
Vincent Pyne.
We trained at Hendon together.
He did close protection.
advanced driver.
tach adviser before he went
to NCA and ended up at Six.
I need him reassigned
to this op.
I can trust him. Isabel.
Very well.
I'll do my best for you.
but I am under a lot of pressure
from the Foreign Secretary.
He is asking me for
regular updates.
So. from this point on.
you need to tell me...
every development the
minute it happens.
Of course. Bianca...
every development.
What? "Norman. it's me."
I know it's you otherwise
I wouldn't be calling you.
"What do you want?"
I need an address.
I'll talk to my man.
Come on.
We have intelligence that a contract's
been taken out on your life.
'Oh. really. Keith?'
Of course a contract
has been taken out.
Did we really think
the Ancien Regime
would stand idly by
and let River flow?
Sir. I have to recommend that
you do not leave the island
until this is resolved.
We have to be in Tallinn for the
announcement. If we pull out now.
our enemies will have a field
day. You cannot go to Tallinn.
The world needs River.
It's bigger than all
of us. We believe
they've hired a
professional assassin.
Where are you getting this
from? Credible sources
within the intelligence community.
Who's taken out this contract?
We don't have that information.
sir. Does the assassin have a name?
Unknown to us.
So. you don't know
who wants him dead.
and you don't know
who's taking the shot.
But you want to call off an
event of this historic magnitude?
Mr Charles will be extremely
vulnerable in Tallinn.
You're his security.
Make sure he's secure.
and let UDC be UDC.
Yes. sir.
"Let UDC be UDC."
He'll love it.
"Drone four airborne
and transmitting."
Thank you.
Thanks.
Sorry.
No worries. I'm just gonna
have to pat you down.
Raise your arms. Could
you put your arms out?
Do you know what? It's
probably... It's probably that.
Oh. well you're allowed
to have your wallet.
Just gonna check.
All clear.
All good. Yeah.
Here's your phone.
Oh. thank you.
Enjoy the concert.
I will.
One non-alcoholic beer.
You changed.
Yeah. um... Yeah.
'So. I've been given
some information.'
The Jackal's been
contracted for another hit.
Who's the target? All
I have is a codename -
Rodin. You don't
know who it is?
No. Not yet.
What's Isabel say?
I haven't told her-
You haven't told your
boss? What the fuck?
I don't know who I can
trust right now. Vince.
Especially after Belarus.
So. who knew about Belarus?
Er. in 303...
Damian. Osi.
Isabel. obviously.
Carver's on the job now.
so it's a full-blown mole hunt.
What you gonna do about Rodin?
I don't know. man.
How am I supposed to find this man
if I can't trust my organisation?
Yeah.
Sounds like you're fucked. mate.
- Really?
- So. why don't we get you a proper drink.
get a few cocktails.
maybe some shots.
Erm... I've gotta get back to
my daughter. she's on her own.
Where's Paul? He's
on a work trip.
How's that going?
The work trip? The marriage?
It's good. "Good."
Hm.
What do you guys
even talk about?
A college professor
and a gun nut?
Lots of stuff. Like what?
Stuff.
"Stuff."
Shut up.
Fuck.
Fuck!
I'm sorry. No-one's
handed a phone in.
Oh. fuck. Yeah.
I need that phone.
Well. we all need
our phones. Yeah.
Yeah. OK. Thank you.
You know what?
Erm. come with me.
I'm gonna need your number.
Yeah. shall I put it
in? Yeah. Here you go.
Thank you.
There you go. Thanks.
Oh. Jackpot.
Encouraging.
Oh. I see something.
Here it is. Oh. yeah.
You are a hero.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
What's your name?
Erm. Rasmus. Rasmus.
Thank you. Rasmus.
I'm Peter.
Nice to meet you.
Hello?
Ah. God. Jasmine!
Jaz?
What kind of mother are you?
Me and Jasmine have
been waiting for hours.
I want you to see this.
Ahhh!
- Ahhh!
- You OK? Show me. You're OK. you're OK.
Here. take this. Go. Go.
Ugh!
You're gonna tell me where
Norman is. Right now.
Fuck you. Fuck me?
Arrrrrgh! You're in my house!
Tell me everything
I need to know.
Or you die. Right here.
Go ahead.
Do it.
Mum!
Wicked Game
Larry Stoke. you're arrested
for force imprisonment
and intent to cause
grievous bodily harm.
You do not have to say anything.
but it may harm your defence...
♪ What a wicked game to play...
He said you killed his daughter.
Of course not.
Cool.
♪ To make me dream of you
♪ What a wicked thing to say
♪ You never felt this way
♪ What a wicked thing to do
♪ To make me dream of you
♪ And I-I
♪ Don't wanna fall in love...
Hello.
♪ And I-I
♪ Don't wanna fall in love
♪ This world is only
gonna break your heart
♪ You know I-I
♪ This world is only
gonna break your heart
♪ I-I
♪ Don't wanna fall in love
♪ Again
♪ With you...
Subtitles by Sky Access Services
www.skyaccessibility.sky
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm